BACKEND DEVELOPER

Artem Degtyarev

D.E.G.T.Y.A.R.E.V.O.A.R.T.E.M@GMAIL.COM

PROFILE

A qualified software engineer with 5 years experience in the IT field. Decisive, able to ensure the smooth running of ICT systems and to provide IT services. Skilled in operational acceptance testing with new systems.

Looking for a middle to senior backend developer position to learn new technologies and implement them for the betterment of the business.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

BACKEND DEVELOPER AT SKILLBOX. SEPTEMBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

- Implemented integrations with third-party APIs
- Implemented generators reducing memory consumption by 80%
- Achieved 90+% in test coverage on the Backend side

Tech: PHP, Laravel, MySQL, Redis, Docker, RabbitMQ

BACKEND DEVELOPER AT PROSCOM. JULY 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- Design and developed various company projects from scratch as a backend developer
- Implemented integration with third-party APIs
- Made several major CI/CD improvements which allowed to reduce deployment time from 15 to 3 minutes
- Implemented CI/CD for new projects
- · Implemented integration with banking modules and flows
- Accelerated script execution from 4 hours to 10 minutes by rewriting PHP-script in Golang
- Developed an internal employee statistics service in Golang
- Optimized database queries

Tech: PHP, Laravel, PostgreSQL, Redis, Docker, Golang

BACKEND DEVELOPER AT GROWFOOD. MAY 2019 - JULY 2020

- Implemented integration with third-party APIs
- Designed and developed chat bot project from scratch as a full-stack developer
- Performed large analytical SQL queries

Tech: PHP, Laravel, PostgreSQL, Redis, Docker, VueJS

WEB DEVELOPER AT PESHKARIKI. JANUARY 2019 - MAY 2019

- Support for the functionality of the company's website, as well as its revision.
- Rewrote part of the project from JQuery to VueJS and did not break anything.

Tech: Yii, PostgreSQL, VueJS, JQuery, Git

EDUCATION

Plekhanov Russian University of Economics, Moscow Bachelor of the Applied Information Science. September 2014 - June 2018

SKILLS

English - Good working knowledge (B1) SQL - Expert

PHP - Expert Golang - Experienced

Laravel - Expert